webgility.com 2018-11-16

# Privacy Policy - Webgility

**On May 25th, 2018 the EU General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) will go into effect, requiring more rigorous compliance with data anonymity and requests for data erasure. While Webgility has not made any functional changes to the way data is processed for users, we’ve updated this policy for clarity and content.Click here to see our FAQ.**

At Webgility, we place the highest importance on respecting and protecting the privacy of our customers. Our most important asset is our relationship with you. We want you to feel comfortable and confident when using our website. Therefore, we would like to share with you the following principles that govern our information practices and other privacy aspects of our Websites. This privacy statement defines privacy aspects specific to [www.webgility.com](http://www.webgility.com/). Throughout this policy, we refer to information that personally identifies you as "personal information".

## **We protect your information**

We work to protect your personal information from loss, misuse or unauthorized alteration by using industry-recognized security safeguards. 

**We tell you how we use your information**  
When we ask you for information, we will tell you, – or it will be clear – what we need to know to fulfill your request and how the information you provide to us will be used. For example, if you order a product or register for a service from us, we will ask you for your name and contact information such as mailing address, phone number, and e-mail address. In addition to responding to your request, we may use your contact information to tell you about products or services we think might interest you or to invite you to participate in a product or service-related survey. Also, any data submitted to us can be removed safely from our database at your request. For more information on data anonymity and erasure, visit our updated GDPR compliance information. Because of the financial nature of our business, this Website is not designed to appeal to children under the age of 13. We do not knowingly request or receive any information from children.

**We do not sell or rent your personal information to anyone.**

**We do not share your personal information with anyone outside of Webgility for promotional and/or marketing use.**

**We tell you about our relationships with third parties**  
We have limited relationships with third parties to assist us in servicing you, for example, by fulfilling customer orders or providing customer service. These service providers are contractually required to maintain the confidentiality of the information we provide them.

Additionally, we have business partners that provide services, some of which are co-branded. We clearly identify partner services and sites. When you request any of these products or services, you are permitting us to provide your personal information to the partner to fulfill your request. We may disclose your information if we are required to by a law enforcement action such as a court order, subpoena or search warrant.

**We tell you how we use Web technology**  
Like many Websites, we use technology, such as cookies, that allow us to make your visit to our Website easier by recognizing you when you return and help to provide you with a customized experience. 

## **We give you choice and control**

We may use your contact information to tell you about other products we think might interest you. However, if you don't want us to contact you for promotional purposes, you can tell us when you provide the information. Your contact preferences only apply to marketing contact. We may need to communicate with you regarding the usability of your product or critical messages relating to your service or software (such as service messages, subscription renewal notices, critical notices, or legally mandated notices).

You can update or correct your contact information relating to your Webgility account by using our Contact Web pages.

## **You can contact us**

If you have privacy or data anonymity and erasure related questions that are not addressed here, please contact us by visiting [www.webgility.com](http://www.webgility.com/). If we make material changes to any of our privacy policies or practices regarding personal information we will update our statement and post a notice on our site 30 days before they take effect.

Last Updated: May 24, 2018

Makes transferring orders from our website to QuickBooks seamless.

\- Jamie Turpin, SOMS Technologies
